socialnetworkingsite.ca 2014-09-26

# @socialnetworkingsite.ca. Own it today.

## Privacy Policy

### Effective Date: March 1, 2012.

This is the website of socialnetworkingsite.ca ("we" or "us"). We are committed to maintaining the privacy of the information that you provide to us in using this site. The following privacy policy applies to the information we collect from you and how we use and protect it. This privacy policy applies only to this site and does not apply to any third-party websites linked to this site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the contents of any third-party linked website. 

### What information do we collect?

When you register as a user of this site, we collect your email address and payment information.

You may optionally enter your name and street address. You may choose to allow visitors to the site to lookup your name and street-address using your email address. This feature is turned off by default, and must be explicitly turned on by you if you wish to allow this service. You can turn this feature off again at any time. If you turn on this feature, you acknowledge that the information will be available to the public and that you make all disclosures on this site at your own risk.

Additionally, when you visit this site, we automatically collect some non-personally identifiable computer information, such as the type of computer operating system (such as Windows XP or Mac OS) and web browser (such as FireFox or Internet Explorer) you are using, information regarding your Internet service provider, and the frequency with which you visit various parts of this site. We use this information to manage the Website and make it more interesting and useful to you.

### How do we use the information we collect?

The information we collect is used to communicate with users regarding their account, improve the content of this site, customize the content and/or layout of this site for each individual visitor, notify consumers about updates to this site, and contact consumers for marketing purposes. The information we collect is shared as necessary with agents or contractors who assist in providing support for our internal operations. The information we collect is disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing this site and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of this site, and to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate change respecting this site. We never give your sign-up e-mail address or other personally identifiable information to advertisers on our website or to other third parties for marketing purposes without your affirmative permission.

### How to opt out of receiving email

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, you should let us know by sending a removal request to us at contact@socialnetworkingsite.ca. We honor all removal requests.

### What are cookies, and how do we use them?

A cookie is a small piece of information that we place in your computer browser to collect information regarding your preferences. We use cookies to identify you when you visit us and to keep track of where you go so we can provide you with a personalized version of this site. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. Cookies could enable us to relate your use of this site to personal information you have provided, but we do not use them for this purpose. You can use your browser settings to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. If you turn off cookies, you will not have access to some of the features that make your experience on this site smoother, and some of our services may not function properly.

### Linked websites

This site may contain links to other websites, including those of sponsors and advertisers. The information practices on those sites may be different from ours and are not covered by our privacy policy. We encourage you to consult the privacy notices on those sites.

### How to request information maintained about you

Upon request, we will provide you with access to all information (including proprietary information) that we maintain about you. You can access this information by emailing us at contact@socialnetworkingsite.ca

### We cannot guarantee the security of this site

We take seriously our obligation to safeguard the confidentiality, security and integrity of personal information collected from our users and have established and will maintain procedures that are designed for that purpose. You should be aware, however, that no system is completely secure from hackers, network failure and error, and we cannot guarantee the confidentiality, security and integrity of information maintained on this site.

### Modification of privacy policy

To accommodate new services and features on this site and to ensure up-to-date compliance with privacy laws, we may modify our privacy policy from time to time. When we modify our privacy policy, we will notify you by a posting on this webpage. Any changes will become effective as of the date of posting with respect to information we then collect in the future. We will treat all personal information we collect, however, in accordance with the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is collected. We urge you to review this privacy policy often so you are always fully informed.

### Contact us

If you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy, please contact us at:

By email: 

contact@socialnetworkingsite.ca 

By regular mail: 

Privacy Request  
socialnetworkingsite.ca  
PO BOX 179  
Coaldale, AB  
T1M1M3  
Canada
